fusionoutsourcing.com 2011-05-22

# FUSION- BPO | Data Entry Services India | Data Mining | Data Cleansing | Data processing India | Medical Billing Services | Medical Billing Company | Medical Billing and Coding

#### **Privacy statement**

FUSION has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to your right to privacy. This document will tell you how and for what purposes we use your information. We are very sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and in general have no objection to User accessing its website without providing any personal information. However there are circumstances like those listed below when FUSION may request you to provide your personal information.

#### **Collection of personal information for propagating business**

In some circumstances, FUSION may request for some personal information from you, like your name, e-mail address, company name, or telephone number. You are at liberty to respond or not to respond to these inquiries and any and all information provided is strictly voluntary. FUSION uses this information to get valuable feedback from your experience on our Web site. In addition, FUSION may also use your personal information for its other business purposes or in order to help serve you better be it by informing you of new services, products, alliances etc that could help you in your business. 

#### **Collecting information for on line surveys**

At times we conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect information from you on the Internet. If you are not happy with the reasons of the survey you may refrain from contributing to it.

#### **Collecting domain information**

FUSION collects domain information and not the email addresses of its visitors as part of its analysis of the use of this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which customers visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. FUSION uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part. By accessing our site you grant your unconditional consent to allow FUSION to collect your domain names.

#### **Disclosure to third parties**

In cases where we believe that business interests will be served, FUSION may share your information with its Business Partners, who can alert you about new products and services to improve your competitive edge. Upon receipt of any alert if you desire to be removed from such alert list, you may inform the sender or unsubscribe from the list as provided in each mail alert. 

#### **Contact Informations**

If you believe that FUSION has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us and we take the necessary action.
